Guide to the Freedom to Marry Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Evan Wolfson Files, 1948-2009; Series I; 20.5; (44 boxes)
  - Press clippings, 1989-2005
    - New York Blade: Massachusetts ruling fuels amendment drive, 2003 November 21 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Pittsburgh Post: same-sex unions, 2003 November 26 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Popping the question, 2003 December 1 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - The New York Times, 2003 December 4 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Waiting at the altar, 2003 December 23 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - People's chronicle: activists predict all-out war on marriage prohibition amendment, 2003 December 26 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Moving toward marriage: how the GLBT community spent its summer, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Windy City Times: Activists declare war on marriage amendment, 2004 January 14 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Cheney would now support federal marriage amendment, 2004 January 15 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - New Jersey governor signs partnership act, 2004 January 15 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Time Out New York issue number 433, 2004 January 15-22 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Bush plans campaign promoting healthy marriage, 2004 January 22 (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - New York Blade: Bush edges closer to marriage amendment, 2004 January 23 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Chicago Daily Law Bulletin, 2004 January 27 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - New York Blade: Battling for gay marriage, 2004 January 30 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - New York Blade LLR 'breaking point' over state DOMAs, 2004 January 30 (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - AM New York: The gay state, 2004 February 5 (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - New York Blade: Massachusetts court says only marriage, 2004 February 6 (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Gay City: Same-sex weddings in Bay State by May, 2004 February 3-11 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - The Washington Post: Bush plans to back marriage amendment, 2004 February 11 (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - Southern Voice: Action! alert adequate response?, 2004 February 13 (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - Massachusetts debated marriage since 2001, 2004 February 13 (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - Wall Street Journal: Judges decide to halt gay weddings, 2004 February 18 (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Bush and gay marriage, 2004 February 25 (Box 37, Folder 61)
    - The Denver Post: Defining marriage, 2004 February 25 (Box 37, Folder 62)
    - The New York Times: But with these words, can I thee quasi-wed?, 2004 February 25 (Box 37, Folder 63)
    - Time for better or for worse, 2004 February 27 (Box 37, Folder 64)
    - Commentary, 2004 February (Box 37, Folder 65)
    - San Jose Mercury news, 2004 March 6 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Philadelphia Inquirer: Gay wedding march likely to be a long one, 2004 March 11 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Press Herald Online: Opponents agree: Heath's idea is a flop, 2004 March 11 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - The Jewish Week: The right to marry, 2004 March 19 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - USA Today: Gay marriage backers seize opportunity, 2004 March 22 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Burelle's collected clippings, 2004 March 30-April 9 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Few in Congress back gay marriage, 2004 April 9 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Honolulu free weekly, 2004 April 7-13 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Marriage equality talk at Fairfield University, 2005 April 11 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - The New York Times Magazine, 2004 April 11 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Comms playing a key role in same sex marriage debate, 2004 April 12 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Time Magazine special issue Time 100, 2004 April 19 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Frank claims at least 50 in house favor gay unions, 2004 April (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - The New York Observer: Church, Hillary regret, 2004 April 21 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Rambler - (Media), 2004 April 21 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Marriage summit, 2004 April 23 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - I can't marry you review, 2004 April 24 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Loud opposition, quiet support, 2004 April 27 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Gay City News: United States Marriage summit convened, 2004 April 29-May 8 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Evan Wolfson as a Time Magazine's 100 most influential people, 2004 April 29 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Romney jilts out-of-state gay couples, 2004 April 30 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Pivotal duty for gay marriage in U.S. hears, 2004 May 2 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Super Size Me's premiere: gay marriage doc at Tribeca New Fest's move and more, 2004 May 3 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - The New York Times: A gay filmmaker looks at gay marriage, 2004 May 6 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Gay City Pataki mum on Massachusetts marriage, 2004 May 6-12 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Burelle's Luce collected clippings, 2004 May 6-16 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Tying the knot documents long struggle for same-sex marriage, 2004 May 12 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Seasoned authors provide reasoned arguments for marriage, 2004 May 13 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Gay leaders aren't rushing to marry, 2004 May 14 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Kerry aims to keep peace with gays, 2004 May 15 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Cape Cod Times: Othersmag benefit from Massachusetts action, 2004 May 16 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Hesitant at first, a movement raced to 'we do', 2004 May 16 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - AM New York: Going to the chapel, 2004 May 17 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Brown vs. Board of Education: 50 years later ruling seen as a model of judicial activism, 2004 May 17 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - CNN.com: Same-sex couples ready to make history in Massachusetts, 2004 May 17 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Los Angeles Times: Massachusetts begins allowing gays to wed, 2004 May 17 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - The Omaha Channel.com: Local same-sex couples will try for licenses, 2004 May 17 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Burelle's Luce collected clippings, 2004 May 17-24 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Bush repeats call for gay marriage ban, 2004 May 18 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Planetout Gov. Romney demands marriage record, 2004 May 18 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Metro weekly: The marriage man, 2004 May 20 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Startribune.com: Doug Grow: Gay marriage pioneers, again, 2004 May 20 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - 365gay.com: New Yorkers march for gay marriage rights, 2004 May 23 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - The Salt Lake Tribune: Amid the laughs, Randall's fussbudget personal helped change society, 2004 May 23 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Newsweek: The "Will & Grace", 2004 May 24 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - SPgate.com: Lawyers gay rights strategy - patience while public adjustion, 2004 May 24 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - President renews support of marriage amendment, 2004 May 27 (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - Gay City News: Thousands turn out for marriage, 2004 May 27-June 2 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - End of the gay rights movement?, 2004 June 1 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - The Village Voice: Generation debt - the new economics of being young, 2004 June 1 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Bay Windows: So they say, 2004 June 3 (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - Join us for an evening to honor Evan Wolfson, 2004 June 3 (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - Burelle's Luce collected clippings, 2004 June 4-13 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Groups up efforts after Massachusetts same-sex marriage ruling, 2004 June 7 (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - Trailblazer Wolfson fight for the freedom to marry, 2004 June 7 (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - At Issue: bordering on equality, 2004 June 8 (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - Florida lawyer flies lawsuit challenging federal DOMA, 2004 June 11 (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - Boston Phoenix: State of matrimony, 2004 June 11-17 (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - Insight CNN transcript, 2003 June 13 (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - Gay People's Chronicles: We are at a civil right's moment, Wolfson says of marriage, 2004 June 18 (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - Gay marriage, federalism, and amending the constitution, 2004 June 20 (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - Letter to the editor from Representative Barney Frank, 2004 June 21 (Box 38, Folder 62)
    - Townhall.com: Media recruiting less credibility, 2004 June 23 (Box 38, Folder 63)
    - Andres Plant: Gay couples will win their fights to wed, 2004 June 25 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Dallas Voice: Tube-turning can't into can, 2004 June 25 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Gay pride parade celebrates new marriage-rights, 2004 June 27 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - America in 2054, 2004 June 28 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Councilman accused of sexual harassment in 2 more cases, 2004 June 30 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Ohio gay marriage, 2004 June (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - American Daily: Media endorse phony diversity, 2004 July 2 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Pride mixes with politics in New York City Pride march, 2004 July 2 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - AM New York: For love or money, 2004 July 6 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Gay groups cheer Kerry's VP choice, 2004 July 6 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Like it or not, 2004 July 8 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Texas Triangle: It won't pass but the Senate vote on the Federal Marriage Amendment will be ugly to watch, 2004 July 9-15 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Naples Daily News: Deroy Mudock: stop licensing marriage, 2004 July 10 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - The 28th amendment, 2004 July 12 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - PlanetOut: Most New England senators reject FMA, 2004 July 13 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Tech Central Station: In private hands, 2004 July 13 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Media matters for America: O'Reilly misled with gay marriage poll; distorted Mass. ruling, 2004 July 15 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Boston Phoenix: Altar-ego, 2004 July 16-22 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Fox News: Senate rejects bid for marriage amendments, 2004 July 15 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - The Miami Herald: A musical plea for gay immigration rights, 2004 July 16 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - PlanetOut News: Poll: Democrats more open to gay marriage, 2004 July 21 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Marriage is a hot topic as gay journalists gather, 2004 July 22 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Gay City News: Kiss me, I'm a Republican, 2004 July 22-28 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Gay marriage as 'the new abortion', 2004 July 26 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Gay newlywed denied passport change, 2004 July 27 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Windy City Times: Same-sex marriage activist Wolfson at "marriage" play, 2004 July 28 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - LGBT leaders work to rid courts of 'trans panic', 2004 July 29 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Thirteen states may vote on gay marriage ban, 2004 July 30 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Library journal review, 2004 July (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Why marriage matters press, 2004 July (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - St. Petersburg Times: The gay marriage divide, 2004 August 1 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Evan Wolfson, and why an open bar matters, 2004 August 3 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Long engagement book review article, 2004 August 5-12 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - The Sunday Oregonian: Judge not, until you've had to judge gay marriage, 2004 August 8 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Gay couples maintain hope, 2004 August 11 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Ever the Advocate: Wolfson has spent all his career fighting for marriage equality, 2004 August 12 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Same-sex issue unresolved despite ruling against SF marriage, 2004 August 12 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Activists gear up for state amendment fights, 2004 August 13 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Gay rights activists weigh tactics of marriage push, 2004 August 13 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Gays suspicious of gov's motivation, 2004 August 13 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Kerry backs no marriage ban, 2004 August 13 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Fenceberry logs off, 2004 August 20 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Marriage flip-floppers, 2004 August 21 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Kansas City.com: Fifty years after Brown v. Board NAACP Legal Defense Fund, 2004 August 22 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Defense of Marriage Act upheld in court, 2004 August 27 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - The American Lawyer: Letter to the editor, 2004 August (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Gay marriage: civil rights or oxymoron?, 2004 September 1 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Plenary: Marriage debate mirrors civil rights struggle, 2004 September 1 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - Conservative opinions, 2004 September 2-3 (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - The New York Times: Film reviews, 2004 September 9 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - Gay couples ask New Jersey High Court for hearing, 2004 September 10 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - The Denver Post: Rights issues frames gay-nuptials battle, 2004 September 19 (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - WEProck, 2004 September 27 (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - The Fight to marry, 2004 October 1 (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - New York Blade: New York Connecticut marriage debate heats up, 2004 October 1 (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - Overthrown Louisiana marriage ban, 2004 October 6 (Box 39, Folder 56)
    - Gay marriage 'caravan' heading to D.C., 2004 October 8 (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - The Washington Times: Marriage amendment defeat stirs questions, 2004 October 10 (Box 39, Folder 58)
    - Tying the knot movie reviews, 2004 October 11 (Box 39, Folder 59)
    - Newsday: Kerry lesbian remark angers Cheney, 2004 October 14 (Box 39, Folder 60)
    - The Salt Lake Tribune: Both sides in debate sharply split over what marriage is, 2004 October 22 (Box 39, Folder 61)
    - The Salt Lake Tribune: 'We are going to win' gay-rights leaders declared at rally, 2004 October 23 (Box 39, Folder 62)
    - Nerve: A dream deferred: what's next for the gay marriage movement, 2004 October 26 (Box 39, Folder 63)
    - The New Republic Online: Self defeat, 2004 October 29 (Box 39, Folder 64)
    - MCGBA legal briefs, 2004 October (Box 39, Folder 65)
    - Immigration website blooded with queries from U.S. anti-Bush visitors, 2004 November 4 (Box 39, Folder 66)
    - Advocate: A failure of will, 2004 November 3 (Box 39, Folder 67)
    - Boise Weekly: Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) storms Salt Lake City, 2004 November 3 (Box 39, Folder 68)
    - State bans on gay marriage galvanizes sides, 2004 November 4 (Box 39, Folder 69)
    - The Wall Street Journal: Gay agender is seen as rallying point, 2004 November 5 (Box 39, Folder 70)
    - Gays take fight on marriage to court, 2004 November 5 (Box 39, Folder 71)
    - Maybe same-sex marriage didn't make the difference, 2004 November 7 (Box 39, Folder 72)
    - Marriage will be spelled out in Texas textbooks, 2004 November 9 (Box 39, Folder 73)
    - Columbians continue to fight for gay marriage, 2004 November 12 (Box 39, Folder 74)
    - BET.com, 2004 November 15 (Box 39, Folder 75)
    - Dallas News.com: Gay-rights activists regroup, 2005 November 15 (Box 39, Folder 76)
    - Times Leader: Election day defeat on same-sex marriage issue sparks debate, 2004 November 16 (Box 39, Folder 77)
    - Breaking up is hard to do for gay couples, 2004 November 19 (Box 39, Folder 78)
    - Gays mark anniversary of marriage ruling, 2004 November 19 (Box 39, Folder 79)
    - Take right road to reform, 2004 November 19 (Box 39, Folder 80)
    - Revision marches to social agenda, 2004 November 22 (Box 39, Folder 81)
    - PlanetOut.com: The marriage-go-round, 2004 November 24 (Box 39, Folder 82)
    - The Nation: Banned in the USA, 2004 November 29 (Box 39, Folder 83)
    - PlanetOut.com: South Africa court rules for gay unions, 2004 November 30 (Box 39, Folder 84)
    - Instinct, 2004 November (Box 39, Folder 85)
    - Gay Life: Jazz brunch highlights gay marriage issues, 2004 December 7 (Box 39, Folder 86)
    - Names to Know: A Wall Street Journal online news roundup, 2004 December 24 (Box 39, Folder 87)
    - Steve Jobs among 15 people to watch in 2005, 2004 December 24 (Box 39, Folder 88)
    - Christianity Today.com: Full court pressure, 2004 December 30 (Box 39, Folder 89)
    - Gay City News: Watch Wolfson, 2004 December 30-2005 January 5 (Box 39, Folder 90)
    - A domestic partnership checklist, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - LaRoche in 2004 Democrat for president: Convict him or kill him: The night they came to kill me (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - NSPeople, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Why marriage matters review, circa 2004 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Between timelines newspaper: National news, 2005 January 6 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - 2004: the year in books and film, 2005 January 7 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - The Indianapolis Star: Same-sex marriage ruling due, 2005 January 16 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - 365gay: Still just a dream, 2008 January 17 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Same sex marriage ban upheld, 2005 January 21 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - 2005 January 26 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - The Post Standard: Advocate urges mobilization for same-sex rights, 2005 January 30 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Setting the docket, 2005 January 31 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Manhattan judge clears the way for same-sex marriages, 2005 February 5 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - The New Federalist, 2005 February 7 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Ala. lawmakers pass bill banning gay marriage, 2005 February 11 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Seattle Post: Intelligencer abstinence, gay marriage, traditional marriage: Valentine's becomes a day for activists, 2005 February 12 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Yahoo!News: In United States, gays try to wed on Valentine's Day, 2005 February 15 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - New York Daily News: Dubya taper: keeping quiet cost me a million, 2005 February 22 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Boalt Hall discussion fleshes out same-sex marriage battle, 2005 February 25 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - The Advocate: Vermonters say gay marriage preferable to civil unions in Connecticut, 2005 February 26-28 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Canadian Lawyer: The passions of Martha McCarthy, 2005 February (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - YahooNews: Group reverses, backs Conn. civil unions, 2005 March 1 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Praying with our feet dancing with our souls, 2005 March 5 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Canada, Spain, set to pass national gay marriage laws, 2005 March 18 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - When tradition, emotion and the law collide on both sides, courts struggle with rationales, 2005 March 20 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Weighing the impact of gay breakups, 2005 March 25 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - The Internet really was for porn, 2005 April 4 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Freedom to Marry taps Fenton to expand PR, 2004 April 5 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Supporters celebrate victory; measure likely to pass house, 2005 April 7 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Marriage underlies civil union debate, 2005 April 10 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - The State life and style, 2004 April 14 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Connecticut steps to forefront on civil unions: geography well organized gay groups spur action, 2005 April 17 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Even Cardinals are prone to peer pressure, 2005 April 17 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - The New York Times: Gay Republicans solider on, one skirmish at a time, 2005 April 17 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - 40 years later, honors for gay-rights pioneers, 2005 April 19 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Bay Window online: Connecticut wins civil unions, 2005 April 21 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Between the Lines Newspaper: The marriage war, 2005 April 21 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Evan Wolfson: The dialogue has just begun, 2005 April 21 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Gay marriage debate heats up, 2005 April 21 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - New law receives mixed reaction in gay community, 2005 April 21 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - TNR Online: Falling forward, 2005 April 21 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Boston Spirit: What we talk about when we talk about marriage, 2005 April/May (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Equality Forum - Philadelphia - "40 heroes", 2005 May 01 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - MSNBC: Judge strikes down Nebraska gay marriage ban, 2005 May 12 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - MSNBC: Marriage ruling sets stage for senate debate, 2005 May 13 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Kansas City Star: As struggles continue elsewhere, Massachusetts marks 1st marriage anniversary, 2005 May 16 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - Civil unions: the debate continues, 2005 May 16 (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - PlanetOut: Gays celebrate year of marriage equality, 2005 May 17 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - Yahoo!News: In other states, opposition solidifies, 2005 May 17 (Box 40, Folder 49)
    - Married gays celebrate 1st anniversary, 2005 May 20 (Box 40, Folder 50)
    - Evan Wolfson: Marriage advocate to speak in San Diego April 21, 2005 May (Box 40, Folder 51)
    - Profnet Wire: Government flaw: medical/same-sex custody, 2005 June 8 (Box 40, Folder 52)
    - The Advocate: A ruling for equality, 2005 June 21 (Box 40, Folder 53)
    - One year after Lawrence v. Texas, 2005 June 25 (Box 40, Folder 54)
    - Writer's case for same-sex unions (Box 40, Folder 55)
    - Now Magazine: Same-sex progress, 2005 July 7-13 (Box 40, Folder 56)
    - There goes the 'neighborhood', 2005 July 8 (Box 40, Folder 57)
    - PlanetOut: United States poll support grows for gay marriage, 2005 August 8 (Box 40, Folder 58)
    - SFgate: Gay issues destined to top court, 2005 August 11 (Box 40, Folder 59)
    - Counterbias: Is this a 'moral' man?, 2005 August 12 (Box 40, Folder 60)
    - Buzzflash: Evan Wolfson brings a lawyer clarity to the discussion of same-sex marriage "rights" and "rites", 2005 August 15 (Box 40, Folder 61)
    - Working for change Buzzflash interview: Evan Wolfson, 2005 August 16 (Box 40, Folder 62)
    - Poll shows increasing support for marriage equality, 2005 August 19 (Box 40, Folder 63)
    - Rehnquist decisions were felt in New Jersey, 2005 September 6 (Box 40, Folder 64)
    - Tying the knot review, 2005 September 7 (Box 40, Folder 65)
    - Bush's social security privatization, circa 2005 (Box 40, Folder 66)
    - Same-sex marriage a year later: for better or for worse, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 67)
    - Along came marry (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Better or Worse: gay groups oppose Ithaca marriage license (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Book reviews (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Brian Ellner campaign brochure (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - City councilmen reviewing gay marriage (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Evil eye for the queer guy ad (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Gay marriage plan upsets activists (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - The Hawaii marriage case launches the US Freedom-to-Marry movement for equality (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - A marriage license: good for this family, good for every family (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - The Marriage muddle (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - National gay marriage debate (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Parents protest scouts policy (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Permanent partners (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Rob Weisbach named president and chief executive officer of Miramax Books and President and CEO of Weinstein Co. new book venture (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Vermont opens new era for gay couples (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Why are right-win groups attacking this family? (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Work now, play later (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Research files, 1983-2007
    - Adoption and foster care by gay and lesbian parents in the United States, 2007 March (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - American values survey initial report, 2006 September 20 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - And justice for all? Litigation, politics and the state of marriage equality today (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Census snapshot: Maryland, 2007 November (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Census snapshot: New Jersey, 2007 September (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Census snapshot: United States, 2007 December (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Center for policy alternatives: progress in the states, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Criminal context violence homosexual panic (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - CRS report for Congress, 2005 December 5 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - David v. Goliath: a report on faith groups working for lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender equality (and what they're up against) (Box 41, Folder 27)